Genevieve Del Rosario

Executive Assistant/Project Coordinator

Granite Falls, WA 98252 eve.delrosario9898@gmail.com 425-737-7278

Friendly and enthusiastic go-getter with five years of customer service experience. Able to learn new tasks quickly and proficient in growing key customer relationships. Represents establishment with friendly, professional demeanor at all times.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Agency Sales Specalist

American Family Insurance - Marysville, WA November 2020 to Present

- Design and implement effective marketing strategies to sell new insurance contracts or adjust existing ones
- Contact potential clients and create rapport by networking, cold calling, using referrals etc
- Appraise the wishes and demands of business or individual customers and sell the suitable protection plans
- Collect information from clients on their risk profiles in order to offer them the proper solution
- Prepare reports to shareholders on the success of your business endeavors
- Retain continuous awareness of transactions, sales and terms and keep relative records
- Check insurance claims to solidify trust and safeguard reputation
- Frequently replenish job-specific knowledge and apply it on the field
- Fulfill all company-established policy obligations
- · Contacting potential clients and creating rapport by networking, cold calling, using referrals etc
- Appraising the wishes and demands of business or individual customers and selling the suitable protection plans

Assistant/Customer Care Representative

Ace Acme Septic Services - Arlington, WA September 2020 to November 2020

- Prepare and mail out reminder notices daily
- Assist in daily dispatching and scheduling
- · Organize and track supply orders
- Assist with processing payments
- Handle ETA queries
- First point of contact on a busy 8-line phone system
- Create and maintain customer databases in Quickbooks
- Prepare correspondence, memos and guotes
- Maintain correspondence on email marketing campaigns

- Receive and assist customers calls and office visitors
- Assist with the organization of promotions and events

Logistics Coordinator

Encompass Logistics - Woodinville, WA June 2020 to August 2020

- Defined helpful metrics and measurements so results could be achieved in a timely manner.
- Oversaw the scheduling for transportation employees on a day-to-day basis.
- Created shipment assignments for carriers based on client timelines.
- Forward client-related service and quality issues to the right party for resolution.
- Complete and oversee traffic and registration documents so transportation issues are reduced.
- Communicate any delays due to weather or other emergencies to the appropriate party to maintain client satisfaction rating of above 90 percent.
- Resolve issues related to customers and related carriers.

Assistant Bookkeeper

Ace Acme Septic Services - Arlington, WA May 2020 to June 2020

- · Assist the bookkeeper in maintaining all financial transactions of a business unit
- Prepare and record day-to-day transactions of a business unit in books and ledgers.
- Process, prepare and record invoices and vendor bills.
- Assist and support bookkeeper in preparing and maintaining accounts receivable and accounts payable records.
- Verify, ascertain and determine the correctness of financial data.
- Prepare and maintain sales records with invoice and payment details.
- Assist and support inventory controller in preparing and maintaining inventory records.
- Track, record and maintain expenditure records with details.
- Assist and support internal and external audit teams.
- Integrate quality programs in bookkeeper assistant activities.
- Answering phones and routing calls to the correct person or taking messages.

Executive Assistant/Project Coordinator

Design Build Services, Inc. - Monroe, WA October 2018 to May 2020

- Answering phones and routing calls to the correct person or taking messages.
- · Handling basic bookkeeping tasks.
- Filing and retrieving corporate records, documents, and reports.
- Greeting visitors and deciding if they should be able to meet with executives.

- Using various software, including word processing, spreadsheets, databases, and presentation software.
- Reading and analyzing incoming memos, submissions, and distributing them as needed.
- Making travel arrangements for executives.
- Performing office duties that include ordering supplies and managing a records database.
- Opening, sorting and distributing incoming faxes, emails, and other correspondence.
- Provide general administrative support.
- Maintaining and monitoring project plans, project schedules, work hours, budgets and expenditures.
- Organizing, attending and participating in job proposal meetings.
- Documenting and following up on important actions and decisions from meetings.
- Preparing necessary presentation materials for meetings.
- Ensuring project deadlines are met.
- Determining project changes.
- Providing administrative support as needed.
- Undertaking project tasks as required.
- Ensuring projects adhere to frameworks and all documentation is maintained appropriately for each project.
- Create a project management calendar for fulfilling each goal and objective.

Waitress / Hostess

Ixtapa Restaurant - Monroe, WA September 2017 to March 2019

- Recorded customer orders and repeated them back in a clear, understandable manner.
- Resolved guest complaints promptly and professionally.
- Took necessary steps to meet customer needs and effectively resolve food or service issues.
- Up-sold additional menu items, beverages and desserts to increase restaurant profits.
- Took initiative to find extra tasks when scheduled duties were completed.
- Maintained a neat, well groomed appearance including impeccable personal hygiene, hair restraint and minimal jewelry that met company standards.
- Quickly and efficiently processed payments and made accurate change.

Administrative Assistant/Receptionist

Rairdon's Chrysler Dodge Jeep Ram of Monroe - Monroe, WA March 2018 to September 2018

- Screened and sorted incoming mail, faxes and deliveries an routed them to the appropriate personnel.
- Organized incoming and outgoing file movements in an efficient and accurate manner.
- Obtained signatures for financial and titling documents and internal invoices.
- · Aggregated and prepared documentation and reports for office meetings, distribution, and filing.
- Answered telephone inquiries from clients, vendors, and the public.
- Received and routed business correspondence to correct department or staff member.
- Greeted customers and visitors in-person and via telephone calls.

General Manager

Snax Gourmet Ice Cream and Hot Dogs - Everett, WA May 2017 to July 2017

- Managed the day-to-day tactical and long-term strategic activities within the business.
- Recruited and hired new staff.
- Reviewed and approved billing invoices and expense reports.

- Directed marketing initiatives.
- Forecasted needs and adjusted future plans.
- Designed promotional materials.
- Prepared standard operating procedures.
- Maximized client satisfaction.

Account Executive

Oasis Communications, Inc - Bothell, WA March 2017 to April 2017

- Answered customers' questions regarding products, prices and availability.
- Emphasized product features based on analysis of customers' needs.
- Collaborated with colleagues to exchange selling strategies and marketing information.
- Maintained friendly and professional customer interactions.
- Shared product knowledge with customers while making personal recommendations.
- Collaborated with members of other departments to complete sales transactions.

Waitress / Hostess

Ixtapa Restaurant - Monroe, WA March 2015 to March 2017

- Recorded customer orders and repeated them back in a clear, understandable manner.
- Resolved guest complaints promptly and professionally.
- Took necessary steps to meet customer needs and effectively resolve food or service issues.
- Up-sold additional menu items, beverages and desserts to increase restaurant profits.
- Took initiative to find extra tasks when scheduled duties were completed.
- Maintained a neat, well groomed appearance including impeccable personal hygiene, hair restraint and minimal jewelry that met company standards.
- Quickly and efficiently processed payments and made accurate change.

Education

High School Diploma in General Studies

Monroe High School - Monroe, WA 2016

Skills

- RECEPTIONIST (2 years)
- CUSTOMER SERVICE (4 years)
- EXCELLENT MULTI-TASKER (4 years)
- PUNCTUAL (6 years)
- Administrative Assistant (3 years)
- Billing (2 years)
- Outlook (2 years)
- Scheduling (1 year)
- · Project Planning

- Project Coordination
- Project Management
- Personal Assistant Experience
- Word Processing (2 years)
- Microsoft Excel
- Leadership Experience
- · Microsoft Office
- · Email Marketing

Certifications and Licenses

Driver's License

Assessments

Receptionist — Highly Proficient

September 2019

Using basic scheduling, attention to detail, and organizational skills in an office setting.

Full results: Highly Proficient

Customer Focus & Orientation — Highly Proficient

September 2019

Responding to customer situations with sensitivity.

Full results: Highly Proficient

Problem Solving — Proficient

October 2018

Measures a candidate's ability to analyze relevant information when solving problems.

Full results: Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.

Additional Information

Skills Reliable and punctual Engaging personality
Delivers exceptional customer service Meticulous attention to detail
Neat, clean and professional appearance Professional and mature
Excellent multi-tasker